thethingsiwant.com 2006-06-23

# TheThingsIWant.com : Privacy Policy

We invite you to contact us if you have questions about this policy. You may contact us by mail at the following address: TheThingsIWant.com

WhiteStripe Inc.  
5445 Collins Ave,  
Suite BTH 1   
Miami Beach, Florida 33141  
United States

You may contact us by e-mail at [service@thethingsiwant.com](mailto:service@thethingsiwant.com) or call us at +1305 867 0244.

### Privacy Statement:

TheThingsIWant.com is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We will never share any personally identifiable information about you with any other organization that could use it to send you unsolicited mail or email without your explicit permission. As a measure of our commitment to your privacy we fully disclose what information we track, how we use it and your role in this process. Our privacy statement answers the following key questions:

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identification is collected from you through the web site
  2. The organization collecting the information
  3. How the information is used
  4. With whom the information may be shared
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under the control of TheThingsIWant.com
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

### Introduction to Privacy

TheThingsIWant.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. TheThingsIWant.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

We collect the following information:

  * HTTP cookies
  * Click-stream data
  * HTTP protocol elements

This data will be used for the following purposes:

* Completion and support of the current activity.
* Web site and system administration.
* Research and development.
* Anonymous user analysis.
* Anonymous user profiling and decision-making.

This data will only be used by ourselves and our agents.

### Registration

In order to set up a personal list of TheThingsIWant.com , a user must first complete the short registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). The User is also asked to make up a password so that their information is protected. This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. We do not require or ask for information on age or income. We give users the option to give us their preferred shipping address, but only so that it may be shared with their potential gifters if they so choose.

### Cookies

Cookies are a technology which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.

Our site makes use of cookies. Cookies are used for the following purposes:

  * Site administration
  * Completing the user's current activity
  * Pseudononymous analysis
  * Pseudonym-based decision-making
  * Research and development

### IP Address

Your IP address is a 12-digit number that is assigned to your computer by the Internet Service Provider each time you log on the Internet. The IP address enables sites that you visit to send data, such as the Web page, to your computer. IP addresses are automatically gathered by the Web server and help us diagnose problems with our server and help us administrate the security and service of the site.

### "Referrer"

A "referrer" is the information sent by your Web browser that references the web URL you linked from, and is automatically gathered by our Web server. This information may be used to identify broad demographic trends of our users.

### Sharing

TheThingsIWant.com does not share any personally identifiable information with anyone without the specific approval of the customer.

TheThingsIWant.com does share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

The user may invite their friends to visit TheThingsIWant.com to see their list of wants in which case the user initiates an email to their friend. TheThingsIWant.com keeps a record of that email address for the sole purpose of that one-time email. If the friend wishes their email address to be removed from our records altogether they may do so by contacting us: [service@thethingsiwant.com](mailto:service@thethingsiwant.com)

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that TheThingsIWant.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### Security

This website takes many precautions to protect our users' information. Users are the only people authorized to alter their personal information. The information collected by this site is stored in a secure operating environment that is not available to the public.

### Site and Service Updates / Choice to Opt-out

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive product information updates about this service and site. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications other than the initial welcoming email. Users can opt-out at the moment of registration or by simply logging on and changing their personal information in "Manage Personal Info".

### Special Offers from Partners and Affiliates / Choice to Opt-in

We **DO NOT** send emails relating to partner offers unless users specifically go to their profile, after registrations, and actively choose to opt-in to this service. If users choose to receive information on products, services or special deals that are presented from time to time by our affiliates and partners they can reverse this choice at any time by logging in and going to profile/ account options.

### Correction/Updating Personal Information:

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, it can be updated easily at the "Manage Personal Info" page. At our website the user is in total control of all their personally identifiable information.

### Legal Disclaimer

We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good faith belief that such information is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on the site.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

### Accountability

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address, The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org, state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at <http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm>

### Contacting the Website

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, this site's privacy practices, or any dealings with the site you are welcome to contact us at: [service@thethingsiwant.com](mailto:service@thethingsiwant.com)

### P3P Compliance.

TheThingsIWant.com is fully P3P compliant, the full p3p privacy policy which corresponds to this human readable privacy policy can be accesed [here](http://www.thethingsiwant.com/w3c/policy.p3p).

The compact policy which corresponds to this policy and is sent to your browser is: CP="ALL DSP COR CURa ADMa DEVa PSAa PSDa OUR STP COM NAV STA"

The following list explains the meaning of each field in the compact policy.

Field Meaning

  * CP= This is the compact policy header; it indicates that what follows is a P3P compact policy.
  * ALL Access to all collected information is available.
  * DSP The policy contains at least one dispute-resolution mechanism.
  * COR Violations of this policy will be corrected.
  * CURa The data is used for completion of the current activity.
  * ADMa The data is used for site administration.
  * DEVa The data is used for research and development.
  * PSAa The data is used for pseudononymous analysis.
  * PSDa The data is used for pseudononymous decision-making.
  * OUR The data is given to ourselves and our agents.
  * STP The data is kept for the stated purpose only.
  * COM Computer information is collected.
  * NAV Navigation and clickstream data is collected.
  * STA State-management data is collected

The compact policy is sent by the Web server along with the cookies it describes. For more information, see the P3P deployment guide at <http://www.w3.org/TR/p3pdeployment>.

### Dispute Resolution and Privacy Seals

We have the following privacy seals and/or dispute resolution mechanisms. If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, Send an email to service@thethingsiwant.com and the Error will be corrected.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address, The DMA's Committee on Ethical Business Practices at mgoldberger@the-dma.org, state or local chapters of the Better Business Bureau, state or local consumer protection office, The Federal Trade Commission by phone at 202.FTC-HELP (202.382.4357) or electronically at <http://www.ftc.gov/ftc/complaint.htm>
